I have a new guest today! This is Frau Tagtraum!
Hello!
Welcome to my channel!
And you love latex, but you said to me you want to try silicone!
Yes, yes! I was so curious about it and I'm like, I'm so excited to try it!
Yeah, so that's what we're doing today. I have a catsuit for you, we have some new masks from Fiturex.
Fiturex, however.
And, yeah, let's, I don't know, let's start.
Or before we start, you want to touch it first?
first? Yes! Maybe I don't know, I don't think so. These are the catsuits. Oh my god they look heavy!
They also have new colors so I'm going to try a red one today.
Okay can I take it off? Yeah. Oh my god it's probably really tough.
Okay, definitely heavier than a latex catsuit.
Yes.
And a lot of scratchiness.
Oh my god, so cool.
First impression, how does the material feel?
It's interesting.
it feels so thick in comparison to latex and yeah it's softer and heavier but I'm
even more curious now to try it. So this is a neck and tricat suit. They have two screws
through the neck but I mean it's really stretchy. Okay okay. And I've worn it and
Pussy worn it so you should fit in there too. Okay okay. Just yeah watch a bit of what
your hair because silicon likes to stick to hair. Yes. But other than that I will give you this water based lubricant.
To lube yourself up and get into it. So I'm sliding in like... Yeah okay.
I will get into this one and we'll see each other again. Yeah okay in a few hours.
And we're back! We're back! We're dressed!
Alright, how was it, dressing this suit? It was an interesting experience.
Good or bad interesting? No, it was actually good. So it was different than putting on a latex catsuit,
because it was like so stiff and with a lot of like lube it was like sliding and you had to pull like harder
it was heavy so if you like tried to like pull it up it was like sliding down
again and you had like it was like a little bit of like a stress situation
but then as soon as it was like over the hips it was like easy to just put it on
it was amazing. How does it feel compared to latex? Because you wear a lot of
latex you like latex how is this? This is also it's different but it's still
amazing because it's tighter I like that it's like more like a hugging feeling
because it's so heavy like a like you have those heavy blankets you put on for
like comfort yeah it's kind of like this so like more tight more heavy and I
actually like the feeling of it so it's different but kind of similar okay so
So what do you like better?
I know that's a mean question.
I think I have to wear that more often to make a conclusion but now I would say latex.
But that's super interesting and I mean probably would need some different things for me to
have it like actually wearing it for like hours but like for like a shooting or like
a little bit of a time it's nice and comfy.
So good first impression.
That was the important part.
So we're wearing the smallest size. We're both wearing the same size. Let's just like turn around.
And since it's so stretchy it adjusts to the body really nice. Mm-hmm. So still tight and
Looks good either way and
We have also a shiner. So if you want to shine it up, this is the matching shiner. Mm-hmm
just up to you yeah you can put it on your hand and just give me a little bit of shine
yeah okay it's just like latex yeah like you make it more shiny yes you can wear
it matte or shiny either way
Even more.
Pretty.
No, you're half shiny.
Half shiny.
I can't turn around.
I mean, you can check in the mirror the difference.
I mean, it's pretty shiny as well, but I also like it matte.
I think both work well.
You have to, like, back as well.
Shiny.
No?
Alright, and since you probably want a full look, let's try a mask.
I mean you also wear latex hoods, so that is not a problem for you?
No.
I mean kind of, so I have like a horny situation and I have body mods.
I have body mods, so I'm sometimes with like latex hoods because they're so tight, I get
a headache.
curious if it's different with the silicone hoods. Okay, which one do you
want to try first? I think I go with this because this one has no eyes.
Okay so for the hood I recommend to use talcum powder so you don't ruin your
hair and makeup. You would with the lube then you would be like squishy so
I'm just sprinkling that inside the hood normally like a generous amount because
I'm just shaking up.
More is better? Yeah, a bit.
Not too much?
And I have a wig cap for you, because it's easier if not...
Not as much hair is touching the teacup.
Now we have...
Maybe it was too much taco.
Like first with my chin?
Yeah.
You have to put it on your chin and hold it there and I will pull it over your head.
It's white.
Okay, no, it's easy.
Oh, uh-huh.
Wait, wait.
Just the collar.
Alright.
Okay, I can't speak if I have to speak.
Yeah, there's something inside. You should check out the FITURUX webpage if you want to know more.
Because we're not going to show this here.
Alright, do you see, can you see anything?
I can see a little bit.
Yeah, the tiny holes.
So you could move around without running into things.
Yeah.
Slow, but yeah.
And how does it feel? Is it tight? Is it wide?
It's comfortable. It's not too tight, but I also have not a lot of movement.
So it's squishy, but it actually feels good.
Nice. You look a bit like an alien cat. I like that.
Do you want to wear some gloves as well?
If you have some, you have a little experience.
Then loop time it is!
I have these nice gloves which have fingernails basically.
Oh, meow meow.
And the second one.
Okay.
Now I don't see any skin anymore.
I would say look at yourself in the mirror, but I doubt you'll see much.
I can see myself.
You can?
Nice. Cute. You look really cute, definitely. Like the little alien cat. Yeah, that's definitely
the term for it. Nice. I think we're going to take some pictures now before you can take
the mask off again. Yeah. That's how you look when you take the mask off and use too much
talk home. I think I look pretty. You do? It's probably good skin care. If you have oily skin then definitely. It's dry forever now.
Alright you can't see anything now but you switched into the second mask but you can like talk still.
I can still talk yeah. Yeah and I can see your mouth through the hole here.
But it looks funny, it looks like a, what did we just say, nautic nofenza?
I like pingu, not nerd.
Pingu, nerd nerd.
Yeah, I think it's really a fun one.
The earrings here are for decorative reasons.
Can you turn around once?
Almost.
Stop!
All right
Okay, since you can't really see yourself
we're going to take some pictures so you can have a look at the pictures afterwards and then
Yeah, I'll help you out of it again
Okay, so would you wear it again?
Definitely yes
That is nice because if you would have come here to try silicone and would have said I don't like it
I would have been sad
Yeah, but it would be also a good experience because then I would know I don't like it
Yeah, but even better than she do like.
Which mask was your favorite?
Um, the second one because it was more comfortable and better fitting.
The cat mask was a little bit looser, but at least I could see something through it.
But yeah, the second one was fun and more unique.
Yeah, Futurix has a lot of masks, so check out their homepage.
I have a discount code which I will write down below in the description text.
I will also link all of your socials. You have Instagram for example, so you can check out her accounts, too
Yeah, I have to say thank you again for joining me
I hope now you know what you can go
Like wish for Christmas. Yeah, I think I have to put it down
Okay, thanks again and yeah, I will see
You at home in the next video, and I hope I'll see you soon again. By the way, we know each other for a while now
I think the first time we did pictures together we can show you these pictures
Yeah, yeah, yeah, you have to attach them on the video
Because it was 2016, 17, something like that
Yeah, I think it was around like 10 years ago
Yeah, we looked a bit different back then
So yeah, we saw each other a lot actually this year, we ran into each other at a lot of events
events, so really happy that you could join me today again.
Thank you for the invite.
Yeah, I'll see you again soon probably.
No worries.
Yes, well, alright.
Have a nice day.
Bye.